[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One type of hair on the human body is called vellus hair. Where is it located?", "correct_answer": "All over the body", "incorrect_answers": ["On the pubic bone", "On fingers and toes", "On the scalp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Brave Little Toaster was about some household appliances that go on a quest to find their owner.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2005 movie is remake of the 1979 film and based on the 1977 Jay Ansen novel of the same name.", "correct_answer": "The Amityville Horror", "incorrect_answers": ["The Echo", "Black Christmas", "The Hitcher"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This word can mean to jump straight up or a foolish and/or weak person.", "correct_answer": "Pronk", "incorrect_answers": ["Zaber", "Clouth", "Phenalk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The BBC series Walking with Dinosaurs, which won three Emmy Awards, consisted of how many parts?", "correct_answer": "6", "incorrect_answers": ["12", "3", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The stars remain in the sky during the day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of the national anthem of Norway?", "correct_answer": "Yes, We Love This Country", "incorrect_answers": ["Glory, Glory", "Oh, Amazing Land", "The Way North"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the exact meaning of the term epiparasite?", "correct_answer": "A parasite whose host is another parasite", "incorrect_answers": ["A specific type of parasite that lives in the human skin", "A parasite that is actually beneficial for its host", "An external parasite that lives on the outside of its hosts body"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete these lyrics from the theme song of a western that was on TV in the 1960s:  \nA soldier of fortune is a man called______________.\n_______________  ______________ where do you roam?.", "correct_answer": "Paladin", "incorrect_answers": ["Chester", "Johnny Yuma", "Sundance"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Sound of Music, the von Trapp Family Singers perform at the Austrian Folk Festival to use as a means to escape the Nazis.  Where did the von Trapp Family Singers place in the competition?", "correct_answer": "first", "incorrect_answers": ["they did not place", "second", "third"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Robert Zemeckis movie was released in 1988?", "correct_answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", "incorrect_answers": ["Who Killed Roger Rabbit", "Toon Patrol", "Return to Oz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the correct order of the premier years of the Blade movies?", "correct_answer": "1998, 2002, 2004", "incorrect_answers": ["1999, 2003, 2005", "1997, 2001, 2003", "1996, 1999, 2004"]}]